var data = [{
	"question":"Who is regarded as father of modern chemistry ?",
	"a":"Ruterford",
	"b":"Einstein",
	"c":"Lavoisier",
	"d":"C.V. Raman",
	"ans":"c"
},{
	"question":"Which is not a type of elements ?",
	"a":"Metals",
	"b":"Non Metals",
	"c":"Metalloids",
	"d":"Gases",
	"ans":"d"
},{
	"question":"Which acid is present in lemon ?",
	"a":"Marlic Acid",
	"b":"Citric Acid",
	"c":"Lactic Acid",
	"d":"Tartaric Acid",
	"ans":"b"
},{
	"question":"Rare gases are",
	"a":"mono atomic",
	"b":"di atomic",
	"c":"tri atomic",
	"d":"None of above",
	"ans":"a"
},{
	"question":"The term PVC used in the plastic industry stands for",
	"a":"polyvinyl chloride",
	"b":"polyvinyl carbobate",
	"c":"phosphor vanadiu chloride",
	"d":"phosphavinyl chloride",
	"ans":"a"
},{
	"question":"What among following is used to produce artificial rain ?",
	"a":"copper oxide",
	"b":"carbon monoxide",
	"c":"silver iodide",
	"d":"silver nitrate",
	"ans":"c"
},{
	"question":"Oil of vitriol is",
	"a":"nitric acid",
	"b":"sulphuric acid",
	"c":"hydrochloric acid",
	"d":"phosphoric acid",
	"ans":"b"
},{
	"question":"Which metal is heaviest ?",
	"a":"Osmium",
	"b":"Mercury",
	"c":"Iron",
	"d":"Nickle",
	"ans":"a"
},{
	"question":"Nail polish remover contains ?",
	"a":"benzene",
	"b":"acetic acid",
	"c":"acetone",
	"d":"petroleum ether",
	"ans":"c"
},{
	"question":"What nucleus of atom contains ?",
	"a":"protons",
	"b":"electrons",
	"c":"electrons and protons",
	"d":"protons and neutrons",
	"ans":"d"
}]